前情提要  你要知道我开这个学校是为了保护这些孩子
Previously on Legacies... You know, I opened this school to protect these kids.
试问我该如何保护他们
How am I supposed to protect them from stuff
免受本不存在之物的伤害呢
that's not supposed to exist?
都是因为我兰顿才会走进这个学校
HOPE: Landon was inside the walls of this school because of me.
都是因为我  他才可以接触到他偷的那把刀
He had access to the knife he stole because of me.
谁挥动它  谁就有力量拯救世界
ALARIC: Whoever wields it has the power to save the world,
或者终结一切生命
or end all life as we know it.
神秘瀑布镇高中的一个穴居人
A Neanderthal from Mystic Falls High
用奶昔泼我
assaulted me with a milkshake.
所以我们就在这里把该做的做完
So let's do what we got to do here.
然后再重回学校
Then let's go back to school.
他们不想让我回学校  没有你我不走
They don't want me there. I am not going without you.
全部奉献
All in.
凯勒布  你在干什么
Kaleb, what are you doing?
听着  我们是兄弟  对吗
Look, we homies, right?
我不会伤害别人  所以你不会说出去吧
And I ain't hurting anybody. Secret's ours?
她为什么动不了了  那个雕像伤了她
Why isn't she moving? The statue hurt her.
萨沙  你在干嘛
Sasha, what are you doing?
拜托老兄  我可是有爱的处男呢
Come on, man. I'm the lovable virgin.
我不该死啊
It's not my time.
我睁开眼睛之后一切都会没事
I'm gonna open my eyes, and everything's gonna be fine.
倒数3
Opening my eyes in three,
two, one.
鬼脸
GhostFace?!
- 别这样  老兄  - 抱歉老兄  你太好吓了
Come on, man. Sorry, bruh. Too easy.
你去哪了
Where were you?
有点饿了
Just got a little peckish.
去拿点夜宵
Went out for a midnight snack.
不生气了吗
We good?
不生气了
Yup. All good. Good.
那晚安
Night, then.
吸血鬼后裔
第一季   第四集
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
谢谢你们能来
ALARIC: Thank you all for coming.
神秘瀑布镇需要我们的帮助  鉴于最近有大量
Mystic Falls needs our help, and given our recent influx
怪物涌入  多诺万警官和我决定
of monsters, Sheriff Donovan and I have decided
我们需要采取果断的行动
we need to take drastic action.
请注意听讲
Please give him your full attention.
正如萨尔茨曼博士所说
Like Dr. Saltzman was saying, local girls
翻 译  霸气小肥鹅
黛娜·莉莲和莎莎·斯托罗克斯昨晚没回来
Dana Lilien and Sasha Stoteraux didn't come home last night.
黛娜有的时候几天不回来去疯玩
Dana sometimes skips town for a few days to party,
但是莎莎这还是第一次
but this is a first for Sasha.
翻 译  噬魂师
谢谢  多诺万警官
Thank you, Sheriff Donovan.
现在刀子不在多里安手里
Now while the knife is away with Dorian
这块也没有什么声音
and things are quiet on his end,
翻 译   swimminglion
所以往最差的想也没什么坏处
it won't hurt to assume the worst.
翻 译 RossyGeng
伙计们  你别给我做鬼脸
Guys... Dude, if you don't stop mugging me.
你听到他说的了
You heard Ol' Blue Eyes.
黛娜有逃跑的习惯
Dana has a history of running away.
我看到你吸她血
I saw you feed on her.
没错  就是吸血而已
Yeah, feed.
不是绑架  MG  我告诉你
Not kidnap. MG, I'm telling you--
- 掏心窝子说  这不是我的事
- vampire to vampire-- this ain't on me.
我需要几个志愿者
Now, I'll need a few of you to volunteer
卧底成为交换生
to go to Mystic Falls High under
前往神秘瀑布镇高中
the guise of an exchange program
目的是  提高我们学校之间的关系
meant to improve relations between our schools,
校 对   霸气小肥鹅
不幸的是  基于现在的状况  很有必要
which, unfortunately, is necessary, given recent events.
特 效   麦 斯
■
看最新热播美剧
上人人视频app
可在线观看 离线缓存
各大应用市场
及AppStore皆可下载
扫描即刻下载
现在我允许你
Now, I give you permission
迫使他们  收集定位咒的材料
to compel them, to gather materials
因为我们能收集到的任何信息
for locator spells, because any information
都可能有很大的不同
we can get will make all the difference.
我想我可以暂时放下我和
Well, I guess that I can set aside my differences
黛娜之间的过节
with Dana for a day,
因为英雄
because that
就该这样
is what heroes do.
我自愿
So... I volunteer as tribute.
她就战斗过一只
She battles
石像鬼  突然就变成了圣母
one gargoyle, and suddenly, she's Mother Teresa.
等我证明你是错了的之后你们肯定会很羞愧
You're gonna be real embarrassed when I prove you wrong.
我加入
I'm in.
我也是
I'm in, too.
我愿意帮忙
I'd like to help.
你是谁
ALARIC: Who are you,
你和霍普·迈克尔森在干什么
and what have you done with Hope Mikaelson?
我就没去过真正的学校
I never got to go to a real school.
我一直想知道成为
I've always wanted to know what it's like
正常的人生活一天是什么感觉
to be a normal for a day instead
而不是成为三种族混血不合群者
of being a tri-brid loner.
这是你自做自受
Yeah, well, that's a bed you made for yourself.
不想听你bb
Not looking for a social lecture.
你打算跟兰登怎么办
So, what's your plan with Landon?
他就在这里呆着了吗
Does he, like, go here now?
怎么  你还想杀他吗
Why? You still thinking about murdering him?
因为那把刀休眠了几个世纪
'Cause there's a knife that sat dormant for centuries
他一拿到手就开始吸引
that started attracting mythical creatures
神话瑞兽了
the day he took possession of it.
要我说我们非常需要了解
I'd say there's a lot we need to learn about him.
然后呢  我们一脚把他踢开吗
And then what? We kick him to the curb?
然后我们要决定
Then we decide to do what's best
什么对学校更好  - 我们在找失踪
for the people of this school. Any idea what to do with him
毒舌女孩的时候该怎么处置他啊
while we search for missing mean girls?
我还真知道
As a matter of fact, yes.
他们说我了吗
Did they say anything about me?
还没
No, not yet.
所有人都在谈论
Everybody's been talking
你之前高中的走失女孩
about some missing girls from your old high school.
他们会开除我吗
Well, do you think they're gonna kick me out?
他们给你了几件衣服
They gave you some clothes.
这应该是好迹象  - 这得是几年前啊
I think that's a good sign. From 1993.
拜托老兄  我们都经历过
Come on, man. We have both been places
没人要我们的时候
where nobody has wanted us before.
- 你懂的  - 是的  低调点
You know the drill. Yeah. Keep my head down,
- 多帮忙  别打架  - 没错
make myself useful, don't pick fights. Exactly.
今天必须顺利进行  兰
We need today to go well, Lan.
我们需要今天完美
No, we need this to go perfect.
否则的话我就跟走了没区别了
Otherwise, I'm as good as gone.
兰顿  借一步说话
Landon. You have a minute?
我觉得你今天会很有用
I think you might be of some use today.
*Mystic Falls, we got claws.*
*On the field, you'll hear us roar. Rawr!*
* If there was a way *
* If there was a way out *
* Well, you could be the first one waiting in line *
* You don't like change *
* So why you want to get out *
* When everything is beautiful *
* It's hard to define *
* Oh... *
抱歉
Sorry. Sorry.
我是在走气场
I was making an entrance, mophead.
抱歉  我就是
Sorry. I just had a...
想到了我大一那年
a flashback to my freshman year here.
女孩失踪了  要么忘记你之前的经历  要么走
Girls are missing, so get your wedgie trauma in check or leave.
她现在好多了  别说了
He's fine now. Let it go.
这样吧
LIZZIE: Okay, here's the deal.
兰登  你去跟你之前的
Landon, you talk to any of the people
校友谈谈
you still know from when you went here.
霍普  尽量不要疏远整个学生
Hope, you try to not deliberately alienate
而我们在拯救世界
the entire student body while the rest of us save the world.
这可不是比赛  莉齐  - 你说得对
This isn't a contest, Lizzie. You're right.
这是 任务
It's a mission
为了英雄和他的
for a hero and her league of...
一群人
whatevers. KALEB: Yeah.
去死吧  我要自己干
Screw that. I work alone.
MG  我需要你冲动
MG, I need your compulsion skills.
你是相当主角还是配角
Would you like to be the Robin to my Batwoman?
事实上  蝙蝠侠并没有罗宾
Actually, Batwoman doesn't have a Robin.
她  就是举个例子  书呆子  我们走  好的
She... Metaphor, nerd. Let's go. Okay.
要知道  狼人一般都是在外面吃
You know, the wolves usually eat outside.
我想跟你在一起
I'd rather hang with you.
开会你没来啊
I didn't see you at the assembly.
我还在熟悉这个地方
Kind of still figuring my way around this place.
你为什么不像兰登一样翘了  去玩侦探游戏
Why didn't you ditch like Landon and go play detective?
我还在练习进攻咒语
Well, I'm actually working on offensive spells for class.
这里只教防守咒语
They only teach defensive magic here,
但是我个人认为  课程需要更新
but I personally think that the curriculum needs to evolve.
怎么了
What?
没什么
Oh, nothing.
怎么了吗
What?
我还在适应
I'm still trying to wrap my head around
这种谈话是正常的
this being a normal conversation here.
这样啊  那么
Got it. So...
你是不是很高兴回来啊
Meaning you're happy to be back?
等我知道兰登可以留下来才会开心
I'll be happy when I know that Landon can stay.
他要是不能呢
And then, what if he can't?
走开  女巫  拉斐尔和我要谈话
Bounce, witch. Rafael and I need to have a little chat.
等我跟乔希说完的
Soon as Josie and I are done.
菜鸟  我是你老大
Actually, newb, I'm your alpha.
我说你完事你就得走
You're done when I say you're done.
这都什么时候了
Well, would you look at the time.
你们这帮直男癌虽然很有趣
As fun as this hurricane of toxic masculinity is,
但是我得上课去了
I have to get to class.
我送你
I'll walk you.
这是高年级楼层
This is the senior hallway,
我的青春期都在这里
where I spent much of my formative years
被塞进每个柜子里  除了这个
stuffed in every locker... except this one.
那个开不开  左手边是厕所
That one doesn't open. On your left, you'll find the bathroom.
那是我第一次被人头塞马桶的时候
It's where I had my first kiss with a toilet.
我没有跟你公开表示敌意
I'm sorry. Is the fact that I'm not openly hostile to you
就意味着我们又成了朋友了吗
make it seem like we're back to being friends?
抱歉我就是  在走放弃治疗路线
Uh, sorry. Just, I was going for effortlessly natural.
但这一切都让我很紧张
But this is all just making me really nervous.
比如回到学校  看到康纳和你在一起
Like, the school and seeing Connor and being with you...
你不是应该跟你认识的人说话吗
Shouldn't you be talking to anyone you know?
说的容易
That's easier said than done.
黛娜的小圈子肯定不会理我
There is no way Dana's clique is talking to me
除非你有能让我变酷的魔咒
unless you have a spell that will make me retroactively cool.
那我去
Well, I'll talk to them, then.
你更惨
It's even worse for you. Trust me.
相信我  你绝对不知道人类高中是怎么回事
You have no idea how human high schools work.
你是新来的  还不如
You're the new girl. Might as well
- 全校曝光呢  - 打扰一下
be radioactive. GIRL: I'm sorry.
你看起来受伤了  这个衰男在骚扰你吗
You look traumatized. Is this loser bothering you?
他想让我买他的混音磁带
He keeps trying to get me to buy his mix tape.
恶心
Gross.
我们去吃饭你饿吗
Well, we're going to lunch. You hungry?
好饿
Famished.
跑步的人上报的
Jogger called it in.
是的  车牌号相符
Yeah, the plates match.
这是黛娜的车
It's Dana's car.
可以断定  她不是逃走的
Think it's safe to say she's not a runaway.
你说这些生物在找
You said the creatures were after a knife
- 你送到远处去的一把到  - 是的  他们在找
- that you had sent far away. ALARIC: They are.
我也把刀送走了
And I did.
这说不通
This doesn't make any sense.
该死
Ah, damn it.
事实上  有个完美的解释
Actually, it's starting to make perfect sense.
是什么
What is it?
吸血鬼的齿痕
A vampire bite.
你是黛娜的朋友  对吧
Nice form. You're one of Dana's friends, right?
吉尔  不要用黛娜的朋友来定义我
Jill, and my friendship with Dana doesn't define me.
那是个玩笑
That was a joke.
当然是
Of course it does.
酷  酷
Cool, cool.
告诉我黛娜和萨沙在哪  我们就不会来烦你了
Tell me where Dana and Sasha are and we'll get out of your hair.
更像是分叉
More like split ends.
闭嘴  萨尔茨曼  你们为什么都要关心她们的事
Shut up, Saltzman. And why are you all up in their business?
你们这些私立学校的孩子都那么神奇的吗
Are all of you private school kids this creepy?
好了  去洗漱吧
COACH: Okay, that's it. Hit the showers.
催眠失败了
Compulsion fail.
霍普现在也许正在为胜利狂欢呢
Hope's probably doing a victory lap by now.
为什么怯场了
What's with the performance anxiety?
我想是你让我分心了
I think you're distracting me.
我穿的是聚酯
I'm wearing polyester.
很美
And you're totally pulling it off.
专心点  MG
Get your head in the game, MG.
你拿着学校的电话
You have the school phone?
你放哪里的
Where were you keeping it?
是你的父亲  他相信我
It's your dad. He trusts me.
你闻起来就像是小熊软糖
You smell like gummy bears.
接电话
Answer it.
好的
Okay.
喂
Hello?
我得和所有人谈谈
I need to talk to everyone.
莉齐
Lizzie.
我告诉过你们要团结协作
I told you to work together.
为了更好得完成任务
LIZZIE: In order to conquer,
我们分开了  老爸
we had to divide, Daddy.
看起来这次你必须
So looks like you're gonna have to trust
相信自己的亲女儿了
your own gene pool for once.
很抱歉让你失望
Sorry to disappoint.
听着  我要告诉你们三件事
Look, I'm about to tell you three things,
都很吓人  我要你们保持冷静
all equally horrifying, so I need you to keep your cool.
你们都能做到吗
Can you both do that?
当然  没问题
Of course, no problem.
一  黛娜死了
Okay. One: Dana is dead.
二  是吸血鬼杀了她
Two: A vampire killed her.
三  我刚和警长说过
Three: I just told the sheriff
我们和此事没关系
that we had nothing to do with it
我现在就得知道  我是对的
so I need to know right now that I am right.
你们中有谁听说
Have either of you heard anything
我们学校有吸血鬼进食的
about the vampires at our school feeding?
没有
No. Nah.
我们不能这样  所有人都知道
We're not supposed to, everyone knows that.
好  很好
ALARIC: Okay. Good.
如果有新消息  我会再打给你们的
I'll call you back when I know more.
还有我希望你们能和霍普一起行动
And I expect you to be with Hope when I do.
你真不擅长说谎
You are a horrible liar.
说吧
Spill.
我来猜猜
Let me guess.
小辫子老实交代了  然后承认
Pigtails spilled her guts and confessed
诱拐了黛娜和萨沙  案件结束
to kidnapping Dana and Sasha. Case closed.
她叫谢丽尔
Her name's Cheryl,
而且不太对
and not exactly.
但她确实邀请我参加啦啦队的选拔
But she did invite me to try out for the cheerleading team.
你现在是谁
Who are you right now?
还有你脑袋上是什么东西
And what is that thing on your head?
这是谢丽尔给我的礼物
It's a gift... from Cheryl.
不戴这个你更好看  霍普
You're better than this, Hope.
放松  屹耳
Relax, Eeyore.
屹耳：小熊维尼里的驴，性格自卑，消沉，和兰登很像
这是黛娜给她的
Dana gave it to her.
这是潜在的定位法术材料
It's potential locator spell material.
再加上  尽管萨沙和康纳在交往
Plus, even though Sasha and Connor are dating,
- 黛娜背着萨沙和康纳睡了  - 这还真是线索
- Dana was sleeping with him behind her back. - Yeah, some clue.
这所学校所有人都知道康纳是种马
Everyone at this school knows Connor's a dick.
拜托  兰登
Come on, Landon.
通奸  失踪的女孩
Adultery, missing girls...
就像是老年人看的电视节目一样
It's like every TV show that old people watch.
他们称作为  冲动犯罪
A "crime of passion," I think they call it.
我认识康纳
I know Connor.
他把我的生活搞得一团糟
He's made my life a living hell,
但他不会杀人  相信我
but he's not a killer. Trust me.
起初就是因为相信你  才让我们身陷囹圄的
Trusting you is what got us into this mess in the first place.
看  他就在那
Look. There he is.
你想当好警察还是坏警察
So do you want to play good cop or bad cop?
我不觉得有中立警察这回事
Because I don't think "emo cop" is a thing.
很有趣
Oh, very funny.
当你在交朋友的时候
But while you were off making friends
我却一个人在那调查
I did some sleuthing of my own.
弗吉尼亚热火队的围巾
Scarf in Virginia heat?
我觉得这听起来才像是线索
Sounds like a lead, I think they call it.
她们是被吸血鬼咬了  里克
MATT: They're vampire bites, Ric.
如果他们说没做  就真的没有做  别乱想了
If they said they didn't do it, they didn't do it. End of story.
事实上  这只是开始  因为我现在
No, actually, it's just the beginning, because now I have
必须把一个17岁的女孩放到运尸袋里
to put a 17-year-old girl in this body bag,
然后向她父母撒谎  编造到底是什么杀了她
then lie to her parents about what actually killed her.
还是你忘了  在这个世界
Or maybe you forgot what it's like
这种谈话是怎样的感觉
to be on this side of that conversation.
这和在哪个世界无关
It's not about sides.
是吗  去和黛娜说啊
Oh, yeah? Tell that to Dana.
我以为我们一起去吃中饭
I thought you said we were gonna have lunch.
是的  我们中的一个
Yeah. Well, uh, one of us is.
* Turn it upside down *
别害怕
Don't be afraid.
* Turn it upside down *
放开她
Let her go.
* Turn it inside out. *
约会结束了
Date's over.
不是我干的  是你自己
It's not me, it's you.
忘掉发生的事  回班上去
Now forget this ever happened and get back to class.
棒极了
LIZZIE: Great.
霍普已经到了
Hope's already here.
我以为我们说好的  兄弟
Thought we were cool, bruh.
别和他称兄道弟
Don't "bruh" him.
不管我是不是第二名  我们知道你杀了黛娜
Second place or not, we know you killed Dana.
等等  黛娜死了
Wait. Dana's dead?
索尔兹曼博士说发现黛娜被吸血鬼咬死了
Dr. Saltzman said they found her dead from a vampire bite.
我没有杀她  所以快从我眼前消失
I didn't kill her, so y'all need to get the hell outta my face.
走吧  伙计们
Come on, guys, let's go.
到了英雄时刻了
It's hero time.
（咒语）
To the Blondemobile.
别着急啊  凯勒布
Not so fast, Kaleb.
我说过了  我只是进食了
I told you, all I did was feed.
随便你们怎么折磨我
Torture me all you want to,
但我的答案不会变
but my answer's gonna remain the same...
因为我没杀黛娜
...because I didn't kill Dana.
他说的对
Uh, he's right.
怎么  你现在能读心了么  兰登
What, so you're a mind reader now, Landon?
我把这称作是直觉
Call it a hunch.
我们在去你们学校涂鸦的路上
DANA: We were on the way to graffiti that mill at your school.
这就是个没什么危害的恶作剧
It was a harmless prank.
但后来我被抓住了
But then I got snatched.
之后我只记得  我在沟渠里醒过来
Next thing I remember, I woke up in a ditch.
你就趁现在尽情高兴吧  莉齐
So enjoy it while you can, Lizzie.
我知道我看起来像个捡垃圾的一样
I'm sure I look like crap.
天哪
Oh, my God.
这是什么
What is that?
这是
It's...
谁来帮帮我
Someone help me out here.
这是所有吻痕的母亲
It's the mother of all hickeys.
你会没事的  黛娜
You're fine, Dana.
你只是有点淫荡
You're just a-a little slutty.
我讨厌你们每个人
I don't even like any of you.
我该去和警察谈谈
I should be talking to the cops.
- 我不能让你去  - （咒语）
- I can't let you do that. - Ad somnum.
我的意思是  她不会让你去的
I mean, she can't let you do that.
所以你没有杀她  而是把她转化成了吸血鬼
So you didn't kill her. You freaking turned her?
转化了她
Turned her?
你觉得我想坐下来听不朽什么的吗
You think I want to sit and listen to that for all eternity?
有人这么做了  也就是说
Well, someone did, meaning that we have
我们手上有个转化期的吸血鬼
a transitioning vampire on our hands.
那我们要怎么处置她
So what are we gonna do with her?
被收养的小子  我一直在找你
Foster kid. I've been looking for you.
我要迟到了
I'll catch up with you later.
我得去上课了
I got to get to class.
听着  杰德  是吧
Look, uh, Jed, right?
- 我不想搞事情  - 我们谁都不想
- I don't want any problems. - Neither do we.
我们就是想邀请你加入团队
We just want to initiate you into the pack.
过程很简单
Okay. The process is simple.
这个月你触发了狼人诅咒
You triggered your werewolf curse this month,
也就是说你最近杀了人
which means you killed somebody recently.
也许是故意的
Maybe on purpose,
也许是无意的
maybe not.
你要做的  就是把你的故事说出来
All you gotta do is tell us the story.
那就是我们的通过仪式
That's our rite of passage.
我不是个喜欢拉帮结派的人
Yeah, I'm not really a pack kinda guy.
你还是不想加入  是不是
You still don't get it, do you?
你没得选
You don't have a choice.
你要么现在加入  要么被教训过后  再加入
You can either submit or you can bleed and then submit.
由你决定
It's your call.
我说住手
I said, hey!
我们会再来的
To be continued.
■
看最新热播美剧
上人人视频app
可在线观看 离线缓存
各大应用市场
及AppStore皆可下载
扫描即刻下载
你还好吗  别碰我
Hey, are you okay? Get off of me!
离我远一点
Just stay away from me.
让我来捋一下
So let me get this straight.
黛娜带着吸血鬼的血死了
Dana died with vampire blood in her system
所以她又复活了
so she came back to life
而现在她正在转变成吸血鬼
and now she's in transition,
而且她需要进食  否则会死
and she needs to feed or die?
搞定了  老兄
MG: Nailed it, bro.
很简单的决定  是吧
Easy decision, right?
所以
All right, so...
我们给她人类的血  就这么简单
we give her human blood, it's that simple.
不是所有人都想获得超能力
Not everyone wants to be supernatural.
有些人只是想当个普通人
Some people just want to be normal.
黛娜受到了精神创伤  这是个重大的决定
Dana's traumatized, you guys. This is a huge decision.
也许我们该给她一到两天的时间
Maybe we should give her a day or two.
如果她不进食  一天内就会死去
She'll be dead in a day if she doesn't feed.
哎呀
Oops.
我数学不好
I suck at math.
你该告诉她实情的
You should tell her the truth.
我猜她一定会喜欢去你们学校
My guess is that she'd be psyched to be
那样的地方的  要是我我会的
at a place like your school... I know I would.
你在那太安静了  MG
You're awful quiet over there, MG.
我是女权主义者  我不会告诉黛娜
I'm a feminist, bruh. I'm not gonna tell Dana
她发生了什么的
what to do with her body.
兰登是对的
Landon's right.
好吧
Ugh, fine.
好吧  但是事先声明  她不能加入训练队
Okay, but to be clear, she is not joining drill team.
咒语
Surgere.
我是晕过去了吗
Did I pass out?
我感觉不太好
I don't feel so well.
我们知道你不舒服
We know how you feel.
没事的  你只是太饿了而已
And it's okay, you're just hungry.
我大二的时候得过厌食症
Anorexia was sophomore year.
这完全是另一回事
This is something else.
你进食之后会好很多的  我保证
You'll feel better after you feed. I promise.
闭嘴吧  我认真的
Oh, shut up. For real.
我甚至一想到进食就会想
Even thinking about eating makes me want to...
妈的  这姑娘吃什么了
Oh, damn. What'd that girl eat?
我觉得她的灵魂刚刚喷射到了我鞋上  恶心
I think her soul just got on my shoes. Ew.
我觉得我也快吐了
I think I'm-a be sick, too.
这样正常吗
Is this normal?
她快把胆汁吐完了
She's puking her guts out.
说真的
Literally.
黛娜  黛娜
Dana. Dana!
我们该通知你爸爸吗
Should we call your dad?
为什么  好让他再训你一顿吗
Why? So he can take another bullet for you?
不要
No.
因为不管是什么  这都不是一个吸血鬼会发生的
Because whatever did this is not a vampire.
这一定是从匕首里出来的另一个怪物
It's got to be another monster from the knife.
那么  或许怪物
Well, maybe the monster's
一直潜伏在我们中间
been right in front of us all along.
什么
What...?
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
之前什么事都没发生过
Hey, none of this started happening until you showed up
直到你出现  偷走了那把匕首
and stole that knife, which is exactly
这没准正是别的怪物来这的目的
what the other monsters came here to do.
- 你觉得这是个巧合吗  - 当然
- You saying it's a coincidence? Yeah.
当然啊
Yeah. Yes, I am.
你们相信我把
You believe me, right?
我知道了
Got it.
不多嘴了
Say no more.
- 拉夫  拉夫  - 我告诉过你让我一个人静一静
- Raf. Raf.  - I told you to leave me alone!
- 不  我不能丢下你不管  不  冷静  - 这不安全
- No, I can't do that until you. No, just calm down! It's not safe!
- 这不安全  闪开  - 冷静一下
- It's not safe! Get away!-  Calm down.
闭上眼睛  深呼吸
Close your eyes and breathe.
深呼吸
Breathe.
像我这样
Just like me.
很好
Good.
深呼吸
Breathe.
很好
Good.
就是这样
That's more like it.
这是什么魔法
Was that magic?
不  只是
No. Just...
和丽兹多年练习的成果  我觉得
years of practice with Lizzie, I guess.
- 我不是有意吓坏你的  - 不会
- I didn't mean to scare you. - No.
你不会吓到我的
You can't scare me.
我害怕的是  如果你不向他臣服  你会丧命
What scares me is that you're dead if you don't submit.
不要
Hey, no,
事情就是这样
it's just the way it is.
你是在跟我谈改变吗
You're the one talking about making change, right?
我是说去参加个选修课  而不是发起一场革命
I meant adding an elective, not launching a revolution.
- 乔茜  - 杰德是头狼  对吗
- Josie - Jed's an alpha, okay?
你是狼人  对吗  事实就是
You're a wolf. Okay? That's just
- 这样的  没有别的办法  - 乔茜
- the way it is. There's no other way. - Josie.
乔茜
Josie?
是萨莎
It's Sasha.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
不  拉夫  我被缠住了
No, Raf, I think I'm stuck.
拉夫
Raf.
什么鬼
What?
好吧  来吧  我们把这事解决了
All right, come on. Let's get this over with.
你想要干嘛  要抽水马桶
What's it gonna be? Toilet bowl?
垃圾桶
Trash can?
还是血淋淋的鼻子
Bloody nose?
说话啊  你这个混蛋
Say something, you dick.
不  你让我活得很痛苦
No, you made my life miserable.
你不能假装我不存在
You don't get to pretend I don't exist.
讨厌  我要离开这
Nasty. Yeah, so, um, I'm out of here.
给个小建议哦
But little piece of advice--
兰登可能在里面
Landon could be in there
犯傻呢
right now eating fools.
所以  我撤啦
So, I'll holla.
好了  大伙
Come on, guys.
如果不是兰登  还有可能是什么呢
If it's not Landon, then what else could it be?
蜘蛛
Spider.
一个大蜘蛛  一个阿剌克涅（拉丁语蜘蛛）
A big spider. An Arachne,
如果你想了解的具体一点
if you want to get specific.
这是书呆子色情片  现实生活中才没有
This is nerd porn, not real life.
龙和石翼魔曾经也是传说呢
So were dragons and gargoyles.
这个作者把她的连环画建立在希腊传说基础上
The writer bases her comics off of Greek lore.
阿剌克涅最初是
An Arachne was originally
一个被嫉妒的上帝诅咒的美丽女子
a beautiful woman who was cursed by a jealous god
变成了一只巨大的蜘蛛
and turned into a giant spider.
它想要变成人类  所以它会
Uh, all it wants is to be human, so it wears
穿着猎物的皮囊
the skin of its prey to pass.
我的天哪  它的尖牙很大
Oh, my God. Its-its fangs are huge,
所以有时伤口会被当做吸血鬼咬痕
so they could pass for a vampire bite.
并且它的咬伤会溶解受害者
And its bite liquefies its victims!
另外  我在黛娜的头发里发现了一张网
Plus, I found a web in Dana's hair.
这就可以解释它为什么不能
That would explain why it couldn't
追随者那把匕首出城了
follow the knife out of town.
一个越野车大小的昆虫想要搭便车出城
An SUV-sized insect can't exactly hitchhike
除非它穿上人类的皮囊
unless it inhabits the body of someone.
- 受害者谁呢  或许是萨莎呢  - 我还是
- Who? Sasha maybe? - My money
赌是你男朋友干的
is still on your boyfriend.
他不是我男朋友  如果我们有它身上的东西
He's not my boyfriend. If we had something from it,
我们就能做一个追踪咒语
we could do a tracking spell.
有它的脸行吗
Would its face work?
太糟糕了  不管我怎么转
This is bad. Whatever spun this,
它都会转回来然后吞噬我们
it's gonna come back and it's gonna eat us.
你不能施法把我们弄出去吗
Can't you witch us out of here?
不能  我的超能力不起作用
No, that's not how my powers work.
我姐姐和我  我们来自一个叫做双子集会
My sister and I, we come from this specific witch bloodline
的特定的女巫家族
called the Gemini Coven.
基本上  我们没有属于自己的超能力
Basically, we don't have powers of our own.
我们必须得从别的东西里吸收法力
We have to siphon them from other things first.
所以  之前你做的
So, that thing that you did earlier,
是从一面墙里吸收法力吗
you siphoned power from a wall?
有一种贯穿整个学校的法力
There's magic that runs through the school.
可以用它来施加一些小型咒语
It works on small spells.
好吧  你能从一个狼人体内吸收法力吗
Okay, can you siphon a wolf?
我觉得  理论上  是可行的
I mean, theoretically, yeah,
但是我的手被缠住了
but my hands are stuck.
除非
Unless...
我没料到会这样
That was unexpected.
抱歉
Sorry.
不用
Don't be.
起作用了吗
Uh, did it work?
我不知道  这些网还在旋转
I don't know. The room's still spinning.
我们被困在这了
Hey, we're trapped up here!
康纳
Connor?
妈的
Damn.
他来了
He's coming.
乔茜
Josie,
现在就是你说的施加
now would be a good time for one of those
进攻魔法的好时机
offensive magic spells you were talking about.
咒语
Ignarious.
好了  我觉得你搞定他了
All right, I think you got him.
或者我们只是把他惹毛了
Or we just pissed him off.
你接吧
It's for you.
我不可能告诉你爸爸我们要去干什么的
No way I'm telling your dad what we're about to do.
我受够了撒谎
I suck at lying.
你很擅长撒谎
You're great at it.
你是他最喜欢的学生
You're his favorite.
你是救世主
You're the hero.
你好呀  爸爸
Hi, Daddy!
我想着打电话给你
Hey, thought I'd call,
看看你  现在怎么样
check in, see how things are going.
很好啊
So good.
真的吗  定义一下很好是什么意思  丽兹
Really? Define "good," Lizzie,
因为我觉得这不包括我发现
because I don't think that involves me tracking down
黛娜的尸体在手套箱里
Dana's body to the glove compartment.
听着  爸爸  没关系的  我们搞定这个案子了
Listen, Dad, it's fine. We cracked the case.
那是一只蜘蛛
It's a spider.
但是  像一只  体型庞大的猪
But, like, a big, huge,
讨人厌的蜘蛛
nasty spider.
而且MG的漫画书上写了怎么杀掉它
And MG's comic books know how to kill it.
漫画书  你认真的吗  丽兹  听我说
Comic books? Really? Lizzie, listen to me,
不管你在想做什么  千万不要做  好吗
whatever you're thinking of doing, don't, okay?
只要告诉我你在哪
So just tell me where you are,
马特和我马上就到
and Matt and I will be right there.
还有  霍普在哪
And where is Hope?
我很抱歉  爸爸
I'm sorry, Dad.
你至少该相信我一次
You're gonna have to trust me for once.
来吧  我们开始吧
Let's do this.
我觉得他还在那
I think he's still out there.
小混球
Hey! Douchebag!
我讨厌蜘蛛
I hate spiders.
- 你得带我们离开这  - 该死
- You need to get us out of here.  - Crap.
咒语
Uanascar.
丽兹  我需要你的帮助
Lizzie, I need your help!
乔茜  拉着我的手
Josie. Take my hand.
跟着我念
Repeat after me.
咒语
Imperium fluctus malleus.
Imperium fluctus malleus!
* Today *
* Today you made me feel irrelevant *
* Twisted my intelligence *
* Made it seem there's no brain in my head *
* I'm like a skeleton, can't shut my eyes *
* All I wanna do is kill somebody *
* Kill somebody *
* Kill somebody like you *
你 你 你
* You, you, you, you *
我只想杀人
* All I wanna do is kill somebody *
杀人
* Kill somebody *
杀像你这样的人
* Kill somebody like you *
你  你  你
* You, you, you, you *
- 她被打了吗  - 没有
- Was she bitten? - No.
你会没事的  森林里有场派对
You're gonna be fine. There was a party in the woods.
你和达娜都很愉快
You and Dana had the time of your lives.
但回家的路上
But on the way home,
你们被山狮袭击了
you guys were attacked by a mountain lion.
你没事了  而达娜却没有
You survived and Dana didn't.
你只能束手无策
There was nothing you could do.
达娜死了吗
Dana's dead?
把记忆都抹掉
Just take it all away.
告诉她别多想
Tell her not to feel anything.
你不能强迫她不悲伤
You can't compel her not to grieve.
我在帮她
I'm helping her.
告诉她  会很伤心的
Tell her that it's gonna hurt.
会一直难受  告诉她
It always will. Tell her
有些时候会比其他人更难过
that some days will be harder than others...
但最终她也会记住
but eventually she'll remember the good times
她和达娜的美好时光
she had with Dana, too.
告诉她记住那些时光
Tell her to hold on to those,
这是熬过这段时间的关键
because it's the key to getting through this.
你确定要这么做吗
Are you sure that you want to do this?
你看到他们怎么对我的了
You saw what they did to me.
我不想再当独狼了
I don't think going lone wolf's an option anymore.
- 你呢  - 看我干嘛
- Do you? - Don't look at me.
我是双胞胎  干什么都不是一个人
I'm a twin. I don't do anything solo.
听好  在凯茜死后
Look, after Cassie died,
兰德勒是我唯一有过的群体
I thought Landon was the only pack that I'd ever have.
我不觉得我还需要其他人
I didn't think that I needed anyone else.
坦白和我说
Be honest with me.
这所学校  这些人
Is this school, these people...
把兰德勒留在这里  值得吗
keeping Landon here-- is it worth it?
这地方很差劲
This place is flawed.
这里的每个人都被诅咒了
Every single person here is cursed in some way,
无论是血统还是人生
whether it's blood or just life.
每个人都有要解决的自身问题
Everyone has issues of their own that they're dealing with.
但我们都是这样
But we're all in this together.
这里的每个人  我们互相关照
Every single person here, we look out for each other.
所以
So, yeah.
这里还是值得的
It's worth it.
好受点了吗
Little help?
实心球
Medicine ball.
杰德和他的兄弟们
Jed and his boys
志在必得啊
play for keeps.
你个养子
Foster kid.
还来干吗
You back for more?
我杀了我女友
I killed my girlfriend.
是个意外
It was an accident.
我在车轮后面  失去控制了
I was behind the wheel, and I lost control.
醒来的时候  就在医院了
When I woke up, I was in the hospital.
兰德勒不得不告诉我她死了
Landon had to tell me that she was dead,
别的我再不知道了
and I don't know anything else.
我现在是群体里的一员了吗
Am I a part of the pack now?
跪下
Take a knee.
什么
What?
你要臣服于你的首领
You're gonna submit to your alpha,
跪下
you take a knee.
我开玩笑呢
No, I'm just playing.
你的球
It's your ball.
你来  拉斐尔  下一轮你来
Do this, Rafael. You're in the next round.
像正常女孩一样过一天
So much for my plan to spend the day
我有好多计划
as a normal teenage girl.
回去还好吗
Did good back there.
还好
Yeah.
在你们说我是怪物前
Felt nice to be part of the team...
我都觉得成为队里一员真好
until you all accused me of being a monster.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
等我们重新信任你之前
It's just gonna take us some time
- 还得花点时间  - 是啊
before we can trust you again. Yeah.
- 我知道  - 一次又一次
- I got that. Repeatedly.
我就一次说个明白吧
So let me lay this out for you all at once.
我不知道我为何会被那把刀吸引
I don't know why I was drawn to that knife
也不知道为何
any more than I can explain
一只超大的蜘蛛寄居在
why a supersized spider inhabited the body
那个欺负我的高中同学体内
of a kid who used to bully me in high school.
我不知道
I don't know
为什么只有在书里才读过的物种
why creatures we've only read about in books
会在神秘瀑布镇作妖
are making cameos in Mystic Falls.
这些我都无法解释
I don't have an explanation for any of this.
说句实话  你也一样
And let's be honest, neither do any of you.
据我观察  我们应该都是一样的
So as far as I can see, we're supposed to be in this together.
今早  我只想
And this morning, all I wanted to be
坐在这里  远离一切是非
was sitting here. Part of all of this.
就和你消磨时光
Spending time with you.
但你整天嘲笑我
But all day long you ridiculed me,
然后在紧要关头
and then you hung me out to dry.
又把我晾在一边
When it mattered.
你想知道正常是什么样吗
You wanted to know what it's like to be normal?
恭喜你啊  霍普
Congrats, Hope.
你终于正常了
You're officially normal.
我明确地说让你等着
I specifically asked you to wait.
- 我知道  但是  - 没有但是
- I know, but... - No buts.
没有但是  丽兹
There are no buts, Lizzie.
平平安安
Okay, being a hero
比成为英雄更重要
is not more important than being safe.
我不是英雄  爸
I'm not a hero, Dad.
我这么做
The only reason
都是因为你就是这样
I was trying to be is because that's how
训练霍普的
you're always treating Hope.
坦诚一点
Let's be honest.
她比我更有天赋
She's better at it than I'll ever be.
霍普不是学习的目标
Hope is not the goal.
霍普是警世之言
Hope is a cautionary tale.
我信任她是因为
And the reasons I trust her
我希望你们也
are the last things I'd ever want
信任她
the two of you to experience.
所以我才成立的这所学校
That's why I founded this school.
所以才有了这些规矩
That's why there are rules.
我们今天之所以还能活着
Well, the only reason why we're alive today
就是因为我们打破了规则
is because we broke the rules.
今天霍普施了个的咒救了我们
Today Hope did a spell that saved us,
如果学校教我们防御魔法
a spell that we would have known
这个咒我们就该知道的
if the school taught us offensive magic.
丽兹昨天差点死了
And then Lizzie almost died yesterday
就因为你没告诉我们
because you didn't tell us
小心怪物
to be on the lookout for monsters.
过去的几天证明了
The past couple of days have proven
你一点都不能保护我们
that you cannot protect us from everything.
我们必须学会自保
We have to start learning how to protect ourselves.
天哪
Oh, God.
这就是他们说的
Is this that moment they talk about
父母失去掌控权得以课吗
when parents lose all control?
爸  爸
Dad. Dad.
没事
All right,
我会好好考虑的
I will take it under consideration.
好吗
Okay?
赶紧睡觉吧
Now... go to bed.
我爱你
I love you.
非常爱
Sort of.
从哪听来的
Where did that come from?
我觉得要发动革命了
I guess I felt like launching the revolution.
你出卖了我
You sold me out!
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know.
丽兹发现我说谎了
Lizzie caught me lying,
- 我就抓狂了  - 什么
- and I-I just crumbled. - What?
兄弟  你得知道自己和谁一伙
Dude, you got to know who you stand with.
不能和那些自以为是的姑娘
And it can't be with some girl
整天厮混
who thinks she's too good to give you the time of day.
色字头上一把刀  懂吗
Vamps before tramps, remember?
是啊
Yeah.
不
N-No.
你这韵押的不错
Look, I appreciate the rhyme,
但不许你不尊重她
but don't disrespect her like that.
我们这有好多怪物呢
We got enough monsters out here as it is.
我们可不能成怪物了
We cannot become one of them.
你是个傀儡  MG
You're a puppet, MG.
是校长
The headmaster
和他女儿的傀儡
and his daughter's little puppet.
- 不  我不是  - 嘛不是
- No, I'm not. - No?
她对你发号施令
Then it doesn't bother you
你就逆来顺受毫不在意   是不是
that she bosses you around and you just take it, right?
他让你干什么
I mean, he makes you run all his errands,
你就帮他干什么
and you just take it.
今天  他们甚至不让我们放她们出来
Even today. They couldn't even let the vamps out on our own.
他们必须派巫师盯住咱们
They had to send the witches to keep an eye on us.
他们甚至规定了我们该吃什么
Hell, they even make rules about how we're supposed to eat,
而他们却不告诉我们  给我们吃了什么
but they don't tell us what they're actually feeding us.
血包就在冰箱里
There's blood bags in that refrigerator right there.
但不是人血
But not human blood!
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你知道吗  兄弟
You know what, man?
问问你自己吧  为什么在院子里
Ask yourself why you don't see many rabbits
看不到有兔子了
running around the yard around here.
- 晚上好  警官  - 我猜猜  你来这
Evening, Officer. Let me guess, you're here
- 来给我奖章的  - 其实  我是来问你几个问题的
- to give me a medal. - Actually, I'm here to ask you a few questions.
- 什么问题  - 为什么
- About what? - About why half
半个神秘瀑布镇的拉拉队
the Mystic Falls cheerleading squad's
脖子上都戴着围巾
wearing scarves around their necks.
走开  马特
Walk away, Matt.
我来解决
I'll handle this.
别装的像来帮我似的
Oh, don't pretend like you on my side
你和他们是一伙的
when you the one who told him.
问题是  谁告诉你的
Question is: who told you?
丽兹  MG
Lizzie? MG?
其实  是你刚刚告诉我的
Actually, you just did.
我有我的怀疑
I've had my suspicions,
但我并没确定就是他们
but I could never confirm them.
所以  你打算怎么办
So... what are you gonna do about it?
我知道你不会把我关起来的
'Cause I know you ain't locking me up.
我干这行太久了  里克
I've been doing this too long, Ric.
如果你的孩子是个威胁的话  我不会放过她们的
If your kids are a threat, I'll be coming for them.
你要是敢威胁我的孩子  警长
If you threaten my kids, Sheriff,
我绝不放过你
I'll be the one coming for you.
好吧  我知道你那为什么安静了
Yeah, well, I know why it's quiet on your end.
我们今天和蜘蛛大战了一场
We had a visit from an ancient body-snatching spider today.
这个进展很有趣啊
Wow, that's an... interesting development.
等一下
Hang on a sec.
你怎么不回家
Listen, why don't you come home?
我们错了
We were wrong.
没人要冲你去
Nothing's coming your way.
话别说太早
Hold that thought.
■
人人视频APP
在线观看美剧
离线高清缓存
更有海量高清电影
扫码即刻下载
特别推荐
■
各大应用市场均可下载
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）